It is the month of Sawan [music] and one is
not ready to have the darshan of Lord Shiva.  How can this be possible
?  Today is the first Monday of Sawan and
I am also fasting.  So come let's get ready for the temple with me.
And here are my
clothes for today.  I am feeling very good wearing this suit.
Now look, I am going to the temple,
so don't do too much heavy makeup.   That
's why for light weight makeup I
will use Face Cada Stroke Cream.  And look,
first I applied it on one side and
blended it well.  And look
how good the glow is on this side because it contains
shea butter and hyaluronic acid which
gives instant glow.  Now I will apply it by mixing three in one
Hydramatte Foundation plus Stroke Cream.
[Music]
Now, with the art of my hands, I
blended it nicely all over my face.  Now lastly my
favourite item is the Compete Wall Lipstick in the
shade Koa Crush and it is smudge proof
too.  The best part is that it can also be used as a blush
and eye shadow.  Now at last
apply stroke cream as a highlighter.
Now my light makeup is done.
Now I will wear my earrings.
Wore my favourite bangles and put a black bindi on my forehead.
And wait, let me do some hair.
And now look at my final look.
Better to go [MUSIC] than not stop.
If you also want these products then
write glow in the comment.  Okay, now I am ready.   Let's go to the
temple.  [Music] And I'm
not alone, with me are my three brothers and